question_bank = {
    'science': {
        '1': {
            'question': 'In what tabular display are the chemical elements typically displayed?',
            'answer': 'Periodic table'
        },
        '2': {
            'question': 'What tissue connects bone to muscle?',
            'answer': 'Tendons'
        },
        '3': {
            'question': 'Anaemia is caused by the deficiency of which mineral in the human diet?',
            'answer': 'Iron'
        },
        '4': {
            'question': 'How is ‘Sound Navigation and Ranging’ more commonly known?',
            'answer': 'Sonar'
        },
        5: {
            'question': 'At room temperature, what is the normal state of the element Mercury?',
            'answer': 'Liquid'
        },
        6: {
            'question': 'Which galaxy is Earth in?',
            'answer': 'The Milky Way'
        },
        7: {
            'question': ' What is the name given to the changing of direction of light as it travels through a lens?',
            'answer': 'Refraction'
        },
        8: {
            'question': 'Elemental gases such as helium, neon, argon and krypton are grouped under what honourable term?',
            'answer': 'Noble gases'
        },
        9: {
            'question': 'What name is given to two metals mixed together, or a metal with another element?',
            'answer': 'Alloy'
        },
        10: {
            'question': 'What is the largest land animal?',
            'answer': 'Elephant'
        },
    },

    'politics': {
        1: {
            'question': 'Who is the current British head of state?',
            'answer': 'Queen Elizabeth'
        },
        2: {
            'question': 'What does the acronym MP stands for in politics?',
            'answer': 'Member of Parliament'
        },
        3: {
            'question': 'Which branch of government is responsible for making laws?',
            'answer': 'Legislative'
        },
        4: {
            'question': 'What is the lower house of the Parliament of the United Kingdom called?',
            'answer': 'The House of Commons'
        },
        5: {
            'question': 'When did the concepts of democracy first originate?',
            'answer': 'Ancient Greece'
        },
        6: {
            'question': 'Who won the 2020 United States presidential election?',
            'answer': 'Joe Biden'
        },
        7: {
            'question': 'Angela Merkel is the current chancellor or head of government in which country?',
            'answer': 'Germany'
        },
        8: {
            'question': 'Who is often considered to be the father of modern political science and political philosophy?',
            'answer': 'Niccolo Machiavelli'
        },
        9: {
            'question': 'Which nickname was dubbed to Margaret Thatcher to refer to her uncompromising leadership and politics style?',
            'answer': ' Iron Lady'
        },
        10: {
            'question': 'The term “politics” first appeared around 460  BC as the title of a book by who?',
            'answer': ' Aristotle'
        },
    },
    'geography': {
        1: {
            'question': 'Which is the tallest mountain in the world?',
            'answer': 'Mount Everest'
        },
        2: {
            'question': 'Which country has the highest population?',
            'answer': 'China'
        },
        3: {
            'question': 'Which is the longest river in the world?',
            'answer': 'The Nile'
        },
        4: {
            'question': 'Mount Everest lies in which mountain range',
            'answer': 'The Himalayas'
        },
        5: {
            'question': 'What are the only two countries to have a land border with the US',
            'answer': ' Canada and Mexico'
        },
        6: {
            'question': 'Which country is also called The Netherlands?',
            'answer': 'Holland '
        },
        7: {
            'question': 'Which state did the US purchase from Russia',
            'answer': ' Alaska'
        },
        8: {
            'question': 'How many countries are there in the United Kingdom? ',
            'answer': '4'
        },
        9: {
            'question': 'What type of leaf is on the Canadian flag? ',
            'answer': 'Maple '
        },
        10: {
            'question': '',
            'answer': ''
        },
    },
}
